

I am highly communicative, organized and hard-working person. Adaptable team player with great interpersonal skills. Fast learner who embraces challenges.

PROJECTS:

Web e-commerce shop - "Igralishte" - Brainster academy

Jan-Feb 2023

- Utilized the Design Thinking Process to deliver user-centered and responsive design solutions.
- Conducted moderated exploratory usability testing with a sample of four participants.
- Demonstrated dedication to incorporating accessibility principles by adhering to Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG).
- Maintained a strong attention to detail in all design work, ensuring high-quality deliverables that met or exceeded client expectations.

Home-cooked food sharing platform - "Jadi domasno" - Brainster academy

Oct-Nov 2022

- For the biggest and most complex project on the academy, the clients chose my team's solution for implementation.
- Created food platform through extensive research, wireframing, and iterative design to meet user needs for easy and convenient food access. Emphasized user needs and pain points to develop visually appealing and user-friendly design.

Website redesign for non-profit organization "Donate a computer" - Brainster academy

Aug - Sept 2022

 Designed and developed a visually appealing and user-friendly website with my team, with a focus on enhancing the hero section. Improved the user experience by redesigning the map and donation counter to enhance information access.

despinavelkovska@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/despina-velkovska 077 708 058

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

UX design (brainstorming, googling, qualitative and quantitative research, analysis, user personas, defining client's objectives/goals, content requirements, functional specifications, user and customer journeys, user flows, site maps)

Ul design (low and high fidelity wireframes, create and manage design systems, creating interactive designs, prototypes, reviewing user's and customer's feedback)

HTML and CSS (basic)

TOOLS:

Figma (and Figiam)

Adobe Suite (xd, photoshop, illustrator)

In vision

Visual Studio Code

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Physiotherapist

- PZU "Viva Medika" Skopje Jan 2021 - Present
- PZU "Medika Nova" Skopje Jun 2020 - Dec 2020
- PZU "Preventiva 99" Skopje May 2015 - Jun 2020

EDUCATION:

Brainster academy of UX/UI design May-Feb 2022

Medical faculty, University "Ss. Cyril and Methodius" - Skopje Bachelor's degree of physiotherapy 2011-2014